Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Energy Fragments
Episode 12
Come on, my Bulala
He became a giant
Brother, stop it
Don’t make the same mistake again and again
Only those with power can decide between wrong and right
Just let me calm him down.
Wolffy
Everyone, be careful
Uncle, don’t make the same mistake again and again.
Change your evil ways and return to the right ways
It’s not your turn to make irresponsible remarks to me
What
Knocked him down
Uncle
This fragment contains too much energy.
It must have flown in through the rift.
And this powerful fragment
I’m afraid only the monster knows its origins
You guys
don’t think you can really defeat me, do you?
Everyone, run quickly
Weslie, Wolffy
That thing of yours can’t deal with me.
stop
With your little strength, you still want to stop me
Weslie
Aren’t you still going to give in?
Sweetie, are you okay?
Ticking is of no use to me
Go quickly
Son, don’t stop
son
Little Cutie, please do me a favor
This is
Send them all away
Actually want to escape?
You can’t deal with Uncle by yourself
Father
Where does this strength in you come from?
You finally know that Golden Bulala is not the strongest force, right?
So now I have this great power
It must be this strange power that makes you become what you are now
I have loved collecting various Bulala since I was a child
But Father said that Bulala is very precious and won’t let me squander it casually.
I’ve wanted to be the King since I was a kid, but you blocked me
But when the monster knocks you away
I finally found the way
how to collect Bulala using the monster
It also takes advantage of everyone’s ignorance about the monster.
Who knew you would be rescued by Sparky again?
Until I got this power
I found that as long as I have enough power,
the Bulala I want,
the throne I want, and the love and respect of the residents—
I can have them all
You are indeed better than me in many ways
but you are not a good king
It seems that you are still being stubborn
Give you one night to think about whether I am a good king or not.
Otherwise I will untie your Heart Knot
Everyone, are you okay?
Fortunately, we are fine
Why
Why Father?
Let’s contact Grandpa Bulala and ask about the current situation in the city.
His Majesty’s Heart Knot
is going to be untied
I want to go back and save Father
Let go, don’t hold me
Sparky, calm down.
If we go back now, we will die.
Aren’t you usually very calm?
At this time, you should be calmer
If you go back now, all His Majesty’s efforts will be in vain.
So shall we do nothing?
Sparky
I thought of a way to save His Majesty
The time has come, my dear brother
How do you think about it?
Still the same sentence
You will never be a good king
Then don’t blame me
Untie his Heart Knot
Ready
start up
What’s going on
How dare you come back?
Bulala flies away as soon as the wind blows
We can transform windmills in the city
Use the wind to blow away Master Quan’s Bulala
Once he loses his strength, we’ll have a chance to fight back.
Transformation is my forte, I’ll do it
Great, that way we have a chance of winning
not enough
Uncle’s ability is too powerful
We must also have the power to compete
I thought of a way to get more power
Then we
split up
Already gone
Why are you back?
We have a way to save His Majesty
you can
Okay
We also need to help
His Majesty used to help us a lot
Now that His Majesty has something to do, we have to do our part for His Majesty.
let’s come together
His Majesty is back after all the hard trip. How can we give up?
I’m coming too
and us too
Then your method is
that’s it
start up
What’s the use of being so big?
There are buildings below the city to block the wind. Look at you.
Everyone, come here quickly. The wind will get stronger in a while.
Don’t underestimate me
Bulala come here quickly
start up
Four windmill cannons, including no blind spots to attack
Look where you run away
I need to run away?
I use Bulala a little more
I can dismantle your windmill
that is
The windmills are broken
All struggles are in vain in the face of absolute power
To be continued